但对我而言不幸的是
Unfortunately for me,
这完全激发了小卡"梁山情义"的一面
it has brought out Cam's "Bromosexual" side.
-史诗级的传球啊  弟兄们  -赞
- Epic throw, bro. - Yeah!
其实这是羊绒上的传球
Actually, that is a cashmere throw,
现在上面有脚印了
which now has a footprint on it.
伙计们  来玩啤乓球吧
Dudes, beer pong!
乓  乓  乓
Pong, pong, pong!
啤酒在冰箱里  弟兄们
Beers are in the fridge, bros.
冰箱  冰箱  冰箱  冰箱
Fridge, fridge, fridge, fridge!
-不  等等  弟兄  -怎么了  亲爱的
- No, hang on, bro. - What's up, sweetie?
你终于归位了
Oh, look who's back.
我发现你今天又请你朋友过来了呢
Um, so I see that you invited your friends again today.
是啊  他们是不是很好玩  你看杰斯多可爱
Yeah, aren't they fun? And how cute is Jace?
我们之前拉过手了
We held hands earlier.
其实是掰手腕  但还是算数啊
We were arm wrestling, but it still counts.
我们找到冰箱了
We found the fridge!
哟  你们做到了
Yo, you did!